Welcome to part three of the first-time homebuyer series today. We're going to be going over inspections
When you're choosing your inspector to inspect the house you're going to buy make sure you do your due diligence and get the most reputable
Inspector make sure the inspector you choose has years of experience good reviews and ask him what does he cover this you do
right on inspection termite inspection make sure you ask and
Most importantly do not pick the cheapest inspector go with the most reputable
Inspect has good reviews good track record that won't screw you over if you do all these steps correctly your inspector should be able to
Find a few things wrong with the home and you should be able to renegotiate the deal again
If you'd like a free homebuyer guide or you see a home ownership on the horizons for you in the next six months to two
Years the MBA directly or call me at nine one seven nine five one two one four two
My name is shurif and I work with homes arrest realty in Staten Island, New York